Kayci North

<u>LinkedIn | kayci.north@gmail.com | Github | Portfolio | 801-503-6095</u>

Software Engineer

Software Engineer pivoting from 14+ years in healthcare. Invested in problem-solving and building solutions to help teams, businesses and communities succeed. Able to constructively contribute diverse viewpoints and solution-oriented approaches to problems that maximize return. Seeking a dynamic job that cultivates creative problem-solving and organizational skills.

Skills

Python | SQL | Postgres | Flask | JavaScript | HTML | CSS | Node.js | MongoDB | Express | React | React Router | Git | Github

Leader | Problem Solver | Detail Oriented | Team Player | Adaptable

Technical Project Experience

Project 4

Happy-Hound- Group Project

De-coupled MERN stack: Mongoose, Express, React and Node.js with full CRUD to make e-commerce store

Mindful

• Full-stack, MVC, CRUD web app with users, sessions, and encryption, to make daily journal entries.

Memory Game

Front-End, HTML, CSS, and Vanilla Javascript to make a 2 player memory game.

Professional Experience

Mountain Top Physical Therapy | Lead Physical Therapist Assistant | Park City, UT

June 2013 - Present

• Managed a team of 3 to problem solve and critically think while practicing patient care.

Mountain Land Physical Therapy | Physical Therapist Assistant | Salt Lake City, UT

August 2011 - June 2013

Multitasker who managed 25 patients daily with the help of a tech

Fit-N-Wise | Physical Therapist Assistant | Decatur, TX

July 2009 - June 2011

Worked PRN for the team of therapist - Able to adapt quickly and critically think

Fit-N-Wise | Physical Therapist Assistant | Decatur, TX

July 2008 - July 2009

• Managed patients with quality care, problem solving and critical thinking

Education

Software Engineering Immersive Certificate: General Assembly | Remote | Nov 2022

420 hour program focused on core full-stack software engineering skills & computer science concepts.

Associates of Science: Physical Therapist Assistant | SouthWestern Oklahoma State University | June 2008

- 10 month program to gain skills, ethics, body science and fundamentals. Clinicals to demonstrate ability to problem solve and critically think while practicing patient care.
- Valedictorian of 2008 graduating class.

Bachelors of Science: Health Sciences/Minor Psychology | Southwestern Oklahoma State University | May 2007

Four-year degree with advanced science and math electives.